I...
Like you, Akihime.
Akihime?
A-Akihime!
Akihime!
I may have done something irreversible.
Hey, hey Yayoi-san! It's been on my mind since summer camp, but...
What is it, what?
The person Sumomo-chan likes...
Sumomo-chan?
It might be Kisaragi-sensei.
Usually, Sumomo-chan is shy.
But if you look, in front of Sensei she is smiling brightly.
I was just thinking the same thing.
I see, so she's in love.
Kisaragi-sensei is fun to talk to.
And he has that manly characteristic about him.
His legs are long too.
Yep, about three times longer than Tsuwabuki's.
Hey! You guys!
Really?
I think the best match for Sumomo-chan is someone who has been with us for a while.
Right?
Haru!
And for that reason, today we're going to have a meeting to talk about it.
Agreed!
What are you talking about?!
Eh?
What is it?
The meeting.
Alright! Two bowls of seconds of Mitsumame. Here you go!
I've been waiting for this!
This, this!
Hey hey hey, so what's this meeting about?
Ahem... the best match for Akihime-san.
The best match for Sumomo?
So you're saying that it's not Kisaragi-sensei?
Who is it?
Huh? Your face is red, Tsuwabuki-kun.
Why did Tsuwabuki's face turn red?
Hmm, now why is that I wonder?
Is it possible?! Could it be?! You like Sumomo-chan!
Then does that mean you've already confessed?
Did you kiss?
Kiss?!
Kiss!
Where? I wonder how many times.
Guys...
Alright! For now, let's all just...
Now now, please calm down.
How can I possibly be calm right now?
Our Tsuwabuki and Sumomo-chan are going to be...
Lovey lovey.
Th-That's why I said it's not like that!
I think that Akihime only thinks of me as a friend.
What do you mean saying weak things like that?!
It's all about guts, guts!
That's right, there is a very good chance, even for Haru.
That's right, everyone let's cheer for Tsuwabuki-kun and Sumomo-chan.
Agreed!
Here.
As our store's special guest I'll give this to you as a present.
Haru isn't very good at talking, so...
"I like you," or...
"Please marry me,"
are things he can't say.
Ma-?!
In those situations, just use a cell phone.
Text messaging is a good idea.
Use emoticons, as they're also convenient.
Stop stalling and do it already!
Do your best, Tsuwabuki-kun.
We're with you on this.
Don't lose to Kisaragi-sensei.
Guys, you know...
If you keep waiting, someone will take her away from you.
If you're looking for Tsuwabuki, he went home already.
It looks like he went to Limelight with everyone.
Limelight is Flora-chan's store, right?
Sumomo, looks like something good happened between you and Tsuwabuki-kun.
Today, Sumomo looks different than usual.
I've watched Sumomo since I was little.
During our elementary school years, when you could finally swing on the bar...
It made me happy to see Sumomo so full of joy.
It's calming.
Today, I'm very happy like I was back then.
Nako-chan.
That was...
A technique that I, the best in Saint Aspalas, have never seen before.
Matsuda.
Yes, Miss!
What do you think?
Yes, my breath was taken away just like you, Miss.
It was more wonderful than anything I've ever dreamed of.
Right, Miss?
Please gather 1000 years worth of Figurare's data right now.
The lake froze in an instant.
With a technique as strong as that...
There should be a clue somewhere.
Nothing, even here.
Wrong, next!
Next! Next! Next! Next!
Next!
That's it!
Moterios Oludin Radium.
A powerful technique that decreases the temperature in the surroundings instantly.
There is no mistake, this is it.
In the long history of Figurare,
only a few prodigies were able to use this technique.
At least for the past hundred years, only one has used this technique.
And that person is...
Karin-sama?
The one who Miss has admired since her childhood?
The legendary Stellar Spinear, the girl genius who broke all the records of Figurare.
Eighteen years ago, Karin-sama went to Retroscena.
No one doubted that she would win the race of collecting the star drops.
But Karin-sama never returned to Figurare.
Never again.
I ended up agreeing to this.
I'll tell you Sumomo-chan's phone number.
I'll give Sumomo-chan Tsuwabuki's number too.
How about you send her a greeting text message first?
Don't worry.
Guts!
I've never thought about messaging...
But still, I want to talk face to face.
My honest feelings.
There's no way that she'd still be here.
What am I expecting?
Sensei...
You know, Sumomo-chan...
We're the only ones here, and there's no one else around.
So you don't need to call me Sensei.
Wow, a picture of them together.
Sensei, did you print two of them on purpose?
I told you, it's not Sensei.
It was embarrassing in front of everyone, so calling you Sensei became a habit.
It's about time we told them about us.
Hmm? It felt like there was someone here...
Dad!
I heard you found something important so I came to see.
Welcome, Nii-san.
Here it is, Dad.
Well, this is nostalgic.
Our wedding photo.
Dad and Mom look wonderful.
As I thought, the one who Akihime likes is Kisaragi-sensei.
I don't want to see anyone tonight.
Also, it's a new moon.
I can remain in my human form.
I don't need to go to Akihime.
Dad and Mom married out of love, right?
Karin-san... your mother, you heard it from her?
Once every hundred years.
The technique that only Karin-sama was able to use. And on her first try.
But that girl... How?
Nee-san sure is pretty.
Stop.
Although I couldn't say it in front of Nee-san.
This is...
It's you.
Please tell me the truth!
This bride is Karin-sama...
The one called the legendary Stellar Spinear, right?
Correct.
And this person is...
I can still remember that event eighteen years ago.
That was a night of miracles no one had ever seen.
Puru Radi Ecresiang
With one spell, Nee-san...
gathered six star drops in a blink of an eye.
Can you believe it?
And then, it was when she was about to gather the seventh star drop.
Gaterius Oludin Radium
Both of them fell in love at first sight.
Back then humans from Retroscena and humans from Figurare were forbidden to marry each other.
Onee-sama threw away her title of genius Stellar Spinear.
To be in the arms of just one person.
That is Akihime Seishiro.
Sumomo-chan is the daughter of those two.
But by regulations, the whole issue was kept a secret.
Sumomo-chan still doesn't know that her mother was a person from Figurare.
Sumomo-chan, I wonder if I ever told you this...
The first time when I told Karin-san my feelings.
Your feelings?
My heart was beating so fast, that it felt like it was going to stop.
"Am I really the right person for Karin-san?"
"Am I causing trouble for Karin-san?"
That's not true!
Mom was not troubled, because to Mom, Dad was...
When you get to really like someone...
you get so nervous you can't endure it.
Waiting for Karin-san's answer felt so long.
It felt like a million years.
But in truth it was only ten seconds.
Karin-san answered me right away.
I love you too.
Sumomo-chan?
I'm sorry, I have to go back to school!
There is something important I have to do!
Come to think of it, it's been a while since I looked at the night sky alone.
Akihime...
I've finally realized...
No matter who Akihime likes, I like Akihime.
Since when did I, about Akihime...
After becoming Yuki-chan it seemed as though I knew a lot about Akihime.
But it may be that I still don't know anything.
Akihime...
I have something important I want to tell you.
I'll wait at the secret place...
This was two hours ago.
I'll pretend Yuki-chan is here right now.
Then I can have more courage.
I'll get it across, just like Mom. My true feelings, surely...
Tsuwabuki-kun, I'm sorry about yesterday.
It was too nerve-racking. It felt like a dream.
I ran away because I was scared.
I thought I would wake up from the dream.
It was as if I wasn't the girl that Tsuwabuki-kun was thinking of.
I'm not good at talking and I'm uninteresting, so I might disappoint you.
To think like that caused me a lot of pain.
This choked up feeling in my chest was painful.
So...
I feel the same way.
I...
never knew that liking someone would be this painful.
I like you.
There's nothing else I can say.
I can feel that Akihime is here, but the words won't come out.
If I stand in front of Akihime.
Me too.
Tsuwabuki-kun... I like you.
This is...
It's the stray acorn.
Stray?
Let's plant this together.
Thank you for waiting!
Finally!
At last!
Should I summarize and tell?
A couple is born!
I'm jealous, it's their first date!
They probably can't hear our voices.
Sweet...
Those two's world...
It might not work out that well.